<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='yes' ?>
<gamedata>
    <maintainer>
        <contact>+265882370345</contact>
        <mailbox>Ganyaf@gmail.com</mailbox>
        <name>Francis Ganya</name>
    </maintainer>
    <gamename>Weakest Link Emu</gamename>
    <gameversion>1.0</gameversion>
    <overview>A multiplayer quiz game</overview>
    <description>
    The weakest link is a real world  television game show.In this game a group of contestants
    (players) work together to try and win as much money as possibl by answering a series of questions.
    The number of contestants range from 5-9 (varies among versions).If a person answers the question correctly, 
    the money chain moves to the next stage otherwise if wrong the money chain restarts.A contestants has the option of 
    banking the money before answering the question but the chain restarts.If 9 questions are answered correctly and no one banks 
    the money is automatically added to the jackpot and the round stops.The time allowed for each round decreases as the round increases.
    If the contestant takes  too long to answer, it is considered to be incorrect and the answeris given.
    At the end of each round all contestants are allowed to vote for who they think is the weakest link (The person dragging them down) in 
    then just ended round.The one with the most votes is eliminated and if there is a tie the strongest link (The person who had the most correct answers or
    banked the most money) gets to chose who leaves among the "ties'".The strongest link gets to start in the next round and if was voted of
    the second strongest link gets to go first.In the final round an allowance is made to generate more money and there is no voting.
    This is called the tripple stake round which usually spans 90 seconds.After that comes the head-to-head contest in which each of the two remaining 
    contenstants battle it out with 5 questions asked to each contestant.if there is a tie the game continues to a sudden death.The winner gets all the money 
    whilst the loser goes home with nothing. 
    </description>
</gamedata>